yallashop.com 2017-05-29

# Privacy Policy | YallaShop UAE

**PRIVACY POLICY**

YallaShop.com is committed to your right to privacy and we recognize the importance of privacy to our customers and website visitors. By reading this statement you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will keep this policy under review and any changes made from time to time will be posted on this page. This Privacy Policy sets out details of the personal information we collect about you and the ways in which we may use that information.

**Personal information**

YallaShop.com endeavors to collect and use your personal information only with your knowledge and consent. We may gather your information from a purchase through your customer enquiries via email or through our customer services team, when you request product information or, when you register online or enter any promotions or competitions through any channel. For web visitors, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration, the user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. YallaShop.com does not share any personal or private customer information submitted online with third parties. Demographic information may also be requested (such as region or PO Box). This information will be stored, analyzed and used to assist Yallashop.com to improve our services.

The information you provide on the YallaShop.com website and/or other communication channels will be held only by YallaShop.com and its duly authorized agents. Your information will not be given or sold to any outside organization for marketing purposes without your consent.

**Data Collection**

By submitting your personal information you accept that your details and related information will be managed by YallaShop.com. Please note that YallaShop.com may provide aggregate statistics and general information about YallaShop.com customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics and general information will not include personally identifying information.

**Purpose of collecting information**

If you are a YallaShop.com registered customer, we may use your personal information for the purposes of: (a) verifying that you are an authorized user if you call the YallaShop.com customer services, (b) informing you of any service related changes affecting your purchase.

YallaShop.com may also use the personal information for the purposes of: (c) providing you with Yallashop.com and related products and services, (d) informing you of YallaShop.com special offers that we think may be of interest to you. YallaShop.com may also be obliged to disclose your personal information to meet any legal or government regulatory requirements or obligations in accordance with applicable laws.

If you decide that you no longer want to receive information from a particular company, you should contact Yallashop.com directly at [support@yallashop.com](mailto:%20support@yallashop.com) or call 800 2475 3000.

From time to time YallaShop.com also requests information from users via our online surveys and satisfaction questionnaires. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as PO Box and age). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving customer experience.

**Comments and Questions**

YallaShop.com reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. If you have any comments or questions about this Policy or about the information we have gathered about you, please contact YallaShop.com at [support@yallashop.com](mailto:%20support@yallashop.com) or call 800 2475 3000.
